[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Live Forever]
[Episode 14]
Eat it.
Maybe you can get a chance
to be together forever.
Do you
recognize me?
No.
You look very much like
an old friend who was kind to me.
There's something ancient about your scent,
like wood that's been buried underground
for thousands of years.
No one else smells like that.
[Memorial Tablet of Chen Gensheng]
Granny Chen,
is she your mother?
Mother?
She watered and took care of me.
Does that make her a mother?
Your family has passed away.
I can't bring them back to life.
But I promise,
from now on,
you'll want for nothing
and live a peaceful life.
I, Ning Changyue,
always keep my word.
Granny and my brother also said
they would always stay with me.
But they still disappeared.
The neighbors said
I should cry
when the people who love me leave.
But I don't really know how.
I just feel
empty inside.
But it also feels like something
has filled it up.
Have you ever felt this way?
If you were here,
you would definitely be able to tell her
what this feeling is.
Qiu,
I will bring you back.
Marry him.
Song Yiqiu.
You really should start a whole new life,
instead of staying with a thousand-year-old piece of wood like me,
and rotting away
together.
[Live Forever]
See?
The gilt phoenix hairpin from the Southern Tang.
The ice-crackle jade vase from the Yuan Dynasty.
Wu School's Landscape of the Southern Mountains
from the Ming Dynasty.
And the gold-and-silver inlaid pieces
you brought back from Persia.
These are the things
you left behind or lost over
the past three thousand years.
I found everything I could
and brought it all here.
There are also some things
I thought you might like.
The phoenix crown and ceremonial robes of the former dynasty's empress.
They were far too elaborate
for everyday wear,
so I had them taken apart
and used the pearls and kingfisher feathers
to make you a lighter set of jewelry.
The embroiderers here can't compare to those in Southern Qin,
so I had them work overnight
to make a full set of "Hundred Sons, Thousand Grandsons" quilts and curtains.
Although not as exquisite as those in the palace,
they're for good luck.
Oh, right.
I bought a villa with a garden
in the best part of the foreign concession.
The house deed and land deed
are both in the name of Song Baiwei.
In the garden,
I had a whole bed of white roses planted.
They'll be in bloom
by summer.
Are you switching careers
to become an antique dealer
or a jewelry merchant?
Look at all this.
Anyone who didn't know better would think you were preparing a betrothal gift.
It's not a betrothal gift.
It's a dowry.
It's been thousands of years.
I haven't seen you smile like this for a long time.
The life of a mortal couple
is only a few decades.
If you insist on tasting this fleeting sweetness,
then I will give you the grandest fireworks.
I'll make this dream of yours
lavish, dazzling,
and bright enough that,
in the long years to come,
you can look back on this moment
and remember how happy you were.
But Song Baiwei,
if he makes you suffer even the slightest wrong,
I'll make him regret ever being born.
If he can keep you smiling like this,
then smile to your heart's content.
Let it make up for all these thousands of years.
Ning Changyue,
are you serious?
It's been three thousand years.
What I can give you,
besides this half-dead life,
is only these worldly possessions.
Just consider it
a dowry from an older brother to his younger sister.
♪ Watching time flow ♪
♪ Hearing the years sigh softly ♪
♪ Immortality still cannot bring fulfillment ♪
♪ Even if fate has destined us to part ♪
♪ I'll still fight with all I have ♪
♪ And cling to you with all my might ♪
♪ I'd give up immortality ♪
♪ To share this joy and sorrow with you ♪
♪ Don't ask how absurd the ending may be ♪
♪ I'd trade this life for eternity ♪
♪ Then we'd be complete ♪
So these things
have been hidden in your heart for so many years.
Now I've made you sad again.
Qiu.
Even if our red thread is severed,
I'll tie it back together.
Mr. Lin.
You've been looking for me constantly lately,
left me so many messages,
and even came all the way here to tell me
the story behind this marriage certificate.
You should keep it.
Consider it
fulfilling your destiny.
Thank you.
If it weren't for you,
I might never have had the chance to find it again.
If you refuse to change, face the problem, or deal with it,
of course you'll repeat the same mistakes.
Xie He.
Thank you for taking me in.
I'm going to solve my problems now.
Thank you.
I'm going to find my destiny.
Good luck!
Qiu.
Be home
at seven tonight.
I have something important to tell you.
Song Yiqiu!
Song Yiqiu.
Song Yiqiu, look at me.
Don't fall asleep.
Don't fall asleep. Wake up.
Look at me.
Song Yiqiu.
Don't...
Don't call.
I won't die.
Find...
Find Ning Changyue.
Find Ning...
Find...
Song Yiqiu.
Song Yiqiu!
Wake up.
Wake up!
♪ So here is to you ♪
♪ My darling ♪
♪ And here is to you ♪
♪ My friend ♪
♪ Here is to you ♪
♪ My lover ♪
♪ I'll follow you until the end ♪
Hello.
Someone is seriously injured here.
I'm at... I'm at...
What are you doing?
She's injured. She needs to go to the hospital.
♪ So when the fire are burning ♪
If you don't want her wounds
to heal in front of everyone,
dead one second
and bouncing back the next,
only to be taken away for experiments,
put the phone down.
♪ And when the light fades away ♪
♪ When the sky is falling ♪
Qiu.
♪ I'll never let you be alone ♪
Someone tried to kill me.
She took the knife for me.
She got hurt
because of me.
If it weren't for me...
If it weren't for me,
she wouldn't...
That was her own choice,
♪ So here is to you ♪
just like when she saved you in your past life.
♪ My darling ♪
♪ And here is to you ♪
♪ My friend ♪
♪ Here is to you ♪
What's going on?
Why isn't the wound healing?
♪ My lover ♪
Go to the hospital now.
♪ I'll follow you until the end ♪
Doctor.
The patient is in critical condition.
If the knife had been a fraction off, she couldn't have been saved.
She's still in critical condition.
Please wait outside.
Find that person.
Qiu.
Your recovery has slowed down.
Is it because the power of immortality is fading?
Ending immortality with you was just an excuse.
I just wanted to get
the chance to stay by your side.
I got what I wanted.
But...
but I caused you to lie here.
Was I wrong again?
I think I've seen this person somewhere before.
Where was it?
Wu Ya.
Take good care of her.
Don't leave her side.
Xie He.